Guide to the Reference Center for Marxist Studies Pamphlet Collection PE.043
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Bulgaria: Economics (5 pamphlets) (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Ganev, A. and V. Videv. Agro-Industrial Complexes (AIC) - A Form of Expanding the Concentration and Specialization of Agriculture in the People's Republic of Bulgaria. Sofia Press, Sofia, Bulgaria., 1973 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Bulgaria: Women (8 pamphlets) (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Dinkova, Maria. The Social Progress of the Bulgarian Woman. Sofia Press, Sofia, Bulgaria., 1972 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Douhteva, Penka. Why do Bulgarian Women Work. Sofia Press, Sofia, Bulgaria., 1975 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Enhancing the Role of Women in the Building of a Developed Socialist Society. Sofia Press, Sofia, Bulgaria., 1973 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Legal Status of Women in Bulgaria. Sofia Press, Sofia, Bulgaria., 1976 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - The Bulgarian Woman in the Conditions of Socialism. Central Council of the Bulgarian Trade Unions Commission on the Problems of the Working Women., 1973 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Tourlakova, Eleonora. The Bulgarian Woman Student. Sofia Press, Sofia, Bulgaria., 1977 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Women in the People's Republic of Bulgaria. Sofia Press, Sofia, Bulgaria., undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Women in People's Republic of Bulgaria. Bulgarian Women's Committee., 1972 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Bush, George H.W. (1 pamphlet) (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Wheeler, Tim. Bushgate-the Inside Story of a Sordid Career. People's Daily World, New York, NY., 1988 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- C.I.A. (2 pamphlets) (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - CIA Covert Action Threat to the Constitution. Center for National Security Studies, Washington DC., undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Sweeney, Cynthia. CIA and CWA. Communications Workers of America, Local 11500, San Diego, CA., 1975 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Cacchione, Peter V. (4 pamphlets and an article) (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Cacchione, Peter V. Public Speaking a Speaker's Guide Book. Workers Library Publishers, New York, NY. (3 copies), 1942 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Gerson, S. W. Pete Cacchione - His Record. Workers Library Publishers, New York, NY., 1943 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- California (14 pamphlets) (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - After the Elections What Next? How to End Starvation a Message to Followers of Epic and the Utopians. Western Worker Publishers, San Francisco, CA. (1 original, 1 photocopy), undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Carlson, Frank. Let's Get Off the Dime. Communist Party of California, San Francisco, CA. (2 copies), undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - On Strike Shut it Down. San Francisco State Strike Committee., undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Sparks, Nemmy. Can Anything Be Done about Taxes?. Communist Party of Southern California, Los Angeles, CA., undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Spector, Frank. Story of the Imperial Valley. International Labor Defense, New York, NY. (1 original, 1 photocopy), undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - The Fire This Time. W.E.B. DuBois Club of Los Angeles., 1965 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Young, Jack. The People Be Damned!. Daily People's World, San Francisco, CA., undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Canada I (10 pamphlets) (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Kashktan, William. The Enemy is Monopoly! Communist Party of Canada, Ontario., undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Makhotin, V. USSR-Canada: Good-Neighbourly Co-operation. Novosti Press Agency Publishing House, Moscow., 1974 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Morris, Leslie. Peace is in your hands. Labor-Progressive Party, Toronto., 1949 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Tester, Jim. Apprentice Training: East Germany's Secret to Economic Success...A Lesson for Canada? Canada-GDR Committee, Toronto. (2 copies), 1980 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Tester, Jim. Never Again!: Socialist Germany - A power for peace in Europe. Northern Book House, Ontario., 1984 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Tester, Jim. Two Trade Union Worlds. Northern Book House, Ontario., undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - The Jacksons...A Family Showing Canadians Real Leadership. Communist Party of Canada, Ontario., undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - The Marxist Quarterly: Crisis of Confederation. Progress Books, Ontario., 1963 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - The Ukrainian Canadian: Window on a Cultural Heritage. Kobzar Publishing Company Limited, Ontario., 1977 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Canada II (contains convention documents from the Quebec Federation of Labour) (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - No to Plant Shutdowns. Quebec Federation of Labour, Quebec., 1977 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Massive Unionization of the Workers. Quebec Federation of Labour, Quebec., 1977 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Opening Speech of the President: Continued Mobilization Essential. Quebec Federation of Labour, Quebec., 1977 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Regionalization: The QFL Everywhere. Quebec Federation League, Quebec., 1977 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Resolutions. Quebec Federation of Labour, Quebec., 1977 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - The Political Responsibilities of the QFL: A Program for Now. Quebec Federation of Labour, Quebec.`, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Union Education in the QFL: Our Present Objectives. Quebec Federation of Labour, Quebec., 1977 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Canada: Communist Party (16 pamphlets) (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Hunt, Leslie. Well, Vet, What Now., undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - J.S. The Story of the Trial of the Eight Communist Leaders. National Executive Committee of the Canadian Labor Defense League, Toronto., undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Kashtan, William. Why Canada Should Quit NATO. Progress Books, Toronto., 1969 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Morris, Leslie. Liberal Plans and You. Progress Books, Toronto., 1963 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Smith, A. E. Communist Illegality and the New Minister of Justice. National Council for Democratic Rights, Toronto., 1942 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Stewart, William. Fightback. Communist Party of Canada (Ontario), Toronto. (2 copies), undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - The Road to Socialism: The Program of the Communist Party of Canada. Communist Party of Canada. (5 copies, different versions), 1960, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Vote Communist: Elect a Progressive Majority Including Communists to Parliament for Real Change. Communist Party of Canada, Toronto. (2 copies), undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Walsh, Samuel. For a Mass Federated Party of the Working People. Editions Nouvelle Frontiere, Montreal., 1974 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Canada: Fascism (3 pamphlets) (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Report First Canadian Congress Against War and Fascism, Toronto., 1934 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Rose, Fred. 'Fascism Over Canada' An Expose. New Era Publishers, Toronto. (2 copies), 1938 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Canada: Indian Policy (1 pamphlet) (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Swankey, Ben. National Identity or Cultural Genocide a Reply to Ottawa's New Indian Policy. Progress Books, Ontario., undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Canada: Labor (11 pamphlets and a flier) (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - $72.98 Per Week!! Necessary for a Family of Four to Maintain Itself on an Adequate Standard of Living. Workers' Education Association, Toronto., 1948 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Kashton, William. Automation and Labor. Progress Books, Toronto., 1964 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Kashtan, William. Say No to Austerity Fully Employment without Inflation. Progress Books, Toronto., undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Morris, Leslie. New Jobs through New Markets How the Cold War Causes Unemployment. Progress Books, Toronto., 1962 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Salsberg, J.B. M.P.P. Jobs! Jobs! Jobs. Labor-Progressive Party, Toronto., 1950 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - "Sedition" the Bosses' Weapon to Stifle Protest Against Hunger, Exploitation and War!. National Executive Committee Canadian Labor Defense League, Toronto., undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Swankey, Ben. What Great Depression?. Northern Book House, Ontario., 1971 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - The Origin of the One Big Union. One Big Union, Winnipeg., 1919 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Canada: Tim Buck (12 pamphlets) (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Buck, Tim. A Better Canada to Fight for, to Work for, to Vote for. Labor-Progressive Party, Toronto. (2 copies), undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Buck, Tim. A National Front For Victory. Political Bureau of the Communist Party of Canada., 1941 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Buck, Tim. Canada Needs A Party Of Communists! National Initiative Committee to Convene a Communist Constituent Convention, Toronto., 1943 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Buck, Tim. Disarmament Means Peace. Progress Books, Toronto. (2 copies), 1959 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Buck, Tim. For Victory in the War and Prosperity in the Peace. Spadina Riding Labor Committee, Toronto., 1943 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Buck, Tim. Keep Canada Independent. Labor-Progressive Party, Toronto., 1948 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Buck, Tim. Lenin a man for all time. Progress Book, Ontario. (2 copies), 1969 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Buck, Tim. The Crimea Decisions and Your Future. National Executive Committee of the Labor-Progressive Party, Toronto., undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Buck, Tim. Wages and Inflation: A Reply to Donald Gordon. Labor-Progressive Party, Toronto. (2 copies), undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Canada: Quebec (2 pamphlets) (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - For a Socialist Quebec: Manifesto of the Movement for a Socialist, Independent and Democratic Quebec and for Equality between Men and Women. Mouvement Socialiste, Montreal., 1982 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Kashtan, William. T he Fight for Democracy and Social Advance. Communist Party of Canada, Toronto., 1970 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Canada: U.S. Relations (1 pamphlet and a flier) (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Swankey, Ben. Keep Canada Out!: Why Canada Should Not Join the Organization of American States. Canadian Cuban Friendship Committee, Vancouver., 1963 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Canada: Women (2 pamphlets) (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Canada's Women. Progress Books, Toronto., 1963 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Nielsen, Dorise M.P. New Worlds for Women. Progress Books, Toronto., 1945 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Capitalism (31 pamphlets and a flier) (Box 14, Folder 5-8)
  - Allen, James S. The Cartel System. International Publishers, New York, NY., 1946 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Allen, James S. Who Owns America?. New Century Publishers, New York, NY. (3 copies), 1946 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Cacchione, Peter V. Wall Street on the Warpath. New Century Publishers, New York, NY. (3 copies), 1947 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Dennis, Eugene. Indicts the Wall Street Conspirators. National Office Communist Party, New York, NY. (2 copies), 1948 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Forsythe, Robert. The World Gone Mad. New Masses, New York, NY., 1936 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Foster, Wm. Z. World Capitalism and World Socialism. Workers Library Publishers, New York, NY. (3 copies), 1941 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - LaFargue, Paul. The Religion of Capital a Satirical Exposure of Capital's Claims to Sanctity. New York Labor New Company. New York, NY., undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Morris, George. How Wall Street Picks Your Pocket. New Century Publishers, New York, NY. (2 copies), 1946 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - O'Connor, Harvey. How Mellon Got Rich. International Pamphlets, New York, NY., 1933 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Pendrell, Nan and Ernst. How the Rich Live and Whom to Tax. Workers Library Publishers, New York, NY., 1939 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Perlo, Victor. The Dollar Crisis What it Means to You. New Outlook Publishers, New York, NY. (3 copies), 1969 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Rochester, Anna. Wall Street. International Pamphlets, New York, NY., 1932 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Taigin, I. Here's How We See it, Mr. Perkins. New Century Publishers, New York, NY., 1946 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Weiss, Max. What Price Profits?. New Century Publishers, New York, NY. (2 copies), 1947 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Whither Modern Capitalism?. Peace and Socialism Publishers, Prague., 1968 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Political Education: The Two Worlds. International Publishers, New York, NY., 1935 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Capitalism and Socialism (1 pamphlet) (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Leontiev, A. Work Under Capitalism and Socialism. International Bookshop PTY, Melbourne., 1944 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Caribbean (1 pamphlet) (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - McConnell, Donald. Economic Trends and the New Deal in the Caribbean. Council for Pan American Democracy, New York, NY., undated (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Caribbean: Community in Britain (contains an article) (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Caribbean: Community in Britain (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Carter, President Jimmy (5 pamphlets) (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Hall, Gus. Into His 2nd Year- Carter Still Off the Track. New Outlook Publishers, New York, NY. (3 copies), undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Winston, Henry. The Carter Administration's African Policy. Political Affairs Reprints, New York, NY. (2 copies), circa 1978 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Catholic Church (5 pamphlets) (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Catholic Church
- Center for Cuban Studies (contains fliers and other promotional material from the Center for Cuban Studies, New York, NY) (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - A Seminar on Cuban Art at the Havana Biennial. Center for Cuban Studies, New York, NY., 1986 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - CCS May Calendar. Center for Cuban Studies, New York, NY., undated (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Center for Cuban Studies Professional Research Trips, June-December, 1992. Center for Cuban Studies, New York, NY. (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Levinson, Sandra. Dear Center Member/Subscriber. Center for Cuban Studies, New York, NY., 1986 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Levinson, Sandra. Cuba Update. Center for Cuban Studies, New York, NY., 1993 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - French, Howard. Cuba, Long Forbidden, Wins Major Attention Abroad. The New York Times., 1992 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Spanish Classes at the Center for Cuban Studies! Center for Cuban Studies, New York, NY., 1993 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - The Center for Cuban Studies. Center for Cuban Studies, New York, NY., undated (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - The Lifeline Fund of the Center for Cuban Studies. Center for Cuban Studies, New York, NY., undated (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - The Most Comprehensive History of Modern Cuba's Foreign Relations. Center for Cuban Studies, New York, NY., undated (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Centralia (3 pamphlets and a flier) (Box Shared Tamiment 200, Folder 28)
  - Chaplin, Ralph. The Centralia Conspiracy., undated (Box Shared Tamiment 200, Folder 28)
  - The Issues in the Centralia Murder Trial. American Civil Liberties Union, New York, NY., 1920 (Box Shared Tamiment 200, Folder 28)
  - These Are the Facts!. General Defense Committee, Chicago, IL., undated (Box Shared Tamiment 200, Folder 28)
- Chauvinism (3 pamphlets as well as articles and a study guide) (Box Shared Tamiment 200, Folder 29)
  - Perry, Pettis. White Chauvinism and the Struggle for Peace. New Century Publishers, New York, NY. (3 copies), 1952 (Box Shared Tamiment 200, Folder 29)
- Child Labor (2 pamphlets) (Box Shared Tamiment 200, Folder 30)
  - Child Labor Headlines. National Child Labor Committee, New York, NY., 1947 (Box Shared Tamiment 200, Folder 30)
  - Green, William. Child Labor: A Primer for Trade Unions and Study Classes. Workers Education Bureau of America., 1940 (Box Shared Tamiment 200, Folder 30)
- Chile (21 pamphlets) (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - "...Before the eyes and conscience of the world": Beatriz Allende Speaks to the North American People. The Venceremos Brigade, New York, NY. (2 copies), 1974 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Chile: State of War. Women's International League for Peace and Freedom, Philadelphia, PA., 1974 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Chile: The Story Behind the Coup. North American Congress on Latin America, New York, NY., 1973 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Chile Yes! Pinochet No! World Peace Council, Helsinki, Finland. (2 copies), 1970s (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - First Session of the International Commission of Enquiry into the Crimes of the Military Junta in Chile. International Commission of Enquiry into the Crimes of the Military Junta in Chile, Helsinki, Finland., 1974 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Luis Corvalan. Novosti Press Agency Publishing House, Moscow., 1975 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Luis Corvalon: Words from Prison. World Peace Council, Helsinki, Finland. (3 copies), 1975 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Meeting of the Juridical Sub-Commission of the International Commission of Enquiry into the Crimes of the Military Junta in Chile Documents. Juridicial Sub-Commission of the International Commission of Enquiry into the Crimes of the Military Junta in Chile, Berlin, Germany. (2 copies), 1977 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - One year of the rule of terror in Chile. International Commission of Enquiry into the Crimes of the Military Junta in Chile, Stockholm., 1974 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Perlo, Victor. End Fascist Terror and U.S. Imperialism in Chile! New Outlook Publishers, New York, NY. (3 copies), 1974 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Rojas, Rodrigo. In the Hands of Chile's Hangment: The Prison Experiences of Rodrigo Rojas. Communist Party, New York, NY., 1975 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Three Stages in the social and political struggle of the chilean woman. Chilean Committee of the World Congress for International Women's Year, Berlin, Germany., 1975 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Torrado, Osvaldo Dorticos. Letter to the Students of Chile: "The Revolution has not betrayed Cuba; it has fulfilled its ideals." Ministry of Foreign Relations, Havana., 1960 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - With the Chilean People Against Fascism!: International Conference of Solidarity with the Chilean People. World Peace Council, Athens., 1975 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Chile: Allende, Letelier, Miffint (5 pamphlets and a brochure) (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - A Tribute to Orlando Letelier and Ronnie Karpen Moffitt. (2 copies), 1977 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - "...Before the Eyes and Conscience of the World" Beatriz Allende Speaks to the North American People. Venceremos Brigade, New York, NY. (2 copies), undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Corvalan, Luis. Words from Prison. Information Centre of the World Peace Council, Helsinki., undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Landau, Saul. They Educated the Crows: An Institute Report on the Letelier-Moffitt Murders. Transnational Institute., 1978 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Chile: CP Writings (8 pamphlets) (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - "...Before the eyes and conscience of the world": Beatriz Allende Speaks to the North American People. The Venceremos Brigade, New York, NY., 1970s (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - A Comment on the Statement of the Communist Party of the U.S.A. Foreign Languages Press, Peking. (2 copies), 1963 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Corvalan, Luis. Our Democratic Project. Communist Party of Chile, London., 1979 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Demand Freedom for Disappeared Prisoners in Chile! World Peace Council, Helsinki, Finland., 1970s (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Information Bulletin to the Party and People of Chile: Manifesto of the Communist Party of Chile. Communist Party of Chile., 1975 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Luis Corvalan Accuses. Novosti Press Agency Publishing House, Moscow., 1975 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - North, Joseph. What are we doing in China? New Century Publishers, New York, NY., 1945 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Chile: Junta Pinochet (14 pamphlets) (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - A Tribute to Victor Jara. The National Chile Center, New York, NY., 1979 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Chile: A Report to the Freedom to Write Committee. PEN American Center, New York, NY., 1980 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Chile: Bulletin of the International Trade Union Committee of Solidarity with the Workers and People of Chile. International Trade Union Committee of Solidarity with the Workers and People of Chile, Prague., 1980 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Chile Is Not Alone: International Solidarity Conference with the Chilean People. Information Centre of the World Peace Council, Helsinki, Finland., 1973 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Chile: One Year Later. International Organization of Journalists, Prague., 1974 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Chile: State of War. Women's International League for Peace and Freedom, Philadelphia, PA., 1974 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Chilena, Izquierda. United Nations Against Fascism: Events, Statements and Resolutions Related to the Fascist Military Junta of Chile. Foreign Coordinating Committee of the Parties of the Chilean Left., 1975 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Confidential Memorandum of the Chilean Foreign Ministry., 1974 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Demand Freedom for Disappeared Prisoners in Chile! World Peace Council, Helsinki, Finland., 1977 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Letters From Chile. Novosti Press Agency Publishing House, Moscow., 1977 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - List of Leaders of the Popular Unity Government and the Chilean People Arrested by the Military Junta. Coalition Center, Rome., 1970s (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Meeting of the Juridical Sub-Commission of the International Sub-Commission of the International Commission of Enquiry into the Crimes of the Military Junta in Chile Documents. International Commission of Enquiry into the Crimes of the Military Junta in Chile, Berlin., 1977 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - One year of the rule of terror in Chile. International Commission of Enquiry into the Crimes of the Military Junta in CHile, Stockholm., 1974 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Our Task: Isolate Chile's Fascist Junta. World Peace Council, Helsinki, Finland., 1975 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Peace Courier. World Peace Council, Helsinki, Finland., 1973 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Why the Coup in Chile: The view point of the N.Z. Socialist Unity Party. New Zealand Socialist Unity Party, Auckland., 1973 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - With the Chilean People Against Fascism! International Conference of Solidarity with the Chilean People. World Peace Council, Athens., 1975 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Chile: Unions (2 pamphlets) (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Solidarity with the Unions of Chile. Labor Solidarity with Chile, Chicago, IL., undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Solidarity with the Unions of Chile. National Chile Center, New York, NY., undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
- China I (10 pamphlets) (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Hell Over Shanghai. Workers Library Publishers, New York, NY., undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Liu Shao-Chi. On Inner-Party Struggle. New Century Publishers, New York, NY., 1952 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Lu Ting-Yi. Education Must Be Combined with Productive Labour. Foreign Languages Press, Peking., 1958 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Mao Tse-Tung. China's New Democracy., 1943 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Mao Tse-Tung. On People's Democratic Rule. New Century Publishers, New York, NY., 1950 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Schuman, Frederick L. America Russia China. New World Review., 1958 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Stewart, Mawell S. China Revisited. Public Affairs Committee., 1974 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - The Facts Behind the China Daily News Case. Committee to Support the China Daily News, New York, NY., undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Three Major Struggle on China's Philosophical Front (1949-64). Foreign Languages Press, Peking., 1973 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - What We Saw in China By 15 Americans. Weekly Guardian Associates, New York, NY., undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
- China II (16 pamphlets) (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - China in Today's World. A New Communist Party pamphlet, London., 1994 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Constitution of the People's Republic of China. First National People's Congress of the People's Republic of China., 1954 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Dutt, R. Palme. Whither China? New Outlook Publishers, New York., 1967 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Eastern Horizon. Eastern Horizon Press, Hong Kong., 1981 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Field, Frederick V. China's Greatest Crisis. New Century Publishers, New York, NY. (2 copies), undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Lapwood, Ralph. Your Questions About New China. Far East Reporter, New York, NY., undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Lewis, John Wilson. Communist China: Crisis and Change. Foreign Policy Association, New York, NY., 1966 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Mao Tse-Tung. China's New Democracy. Workers Library Publishers, New York, NY., 1944 (Box 16, Folder 1)